rushordertees.com 2019-01-30

# Learn About Our Privacy Policy for RushOrderTees.com™

## Your Privacy Matters

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Printfly Corporation collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the <https://www.rushordertees.com/> website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Printfly Corporation.

**Your Personal Information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Site, place an order, respond to a survey and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, payment information for the purpose of processing your order.

We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities, such as placing an order.  

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser save cookies for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about their Site usage.  Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

Printfly Corporation collects and uses Users' personal information for the following purposes:

• To **improve customer service**

Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs. 

• To **personalize User experience**  

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. 

• To **improve our Site**

We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you. 

• To **process transactions**

We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide service. 

• To **administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature**  

To send Users information about topics we think will be of interest to them, such as monthly mailers, or additional follow up for future business. 

• To **send periodic emails**  

• To **send reminder emails**

The email address Users provide for order processing, will be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It will also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. Every User is deciding to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we allow Users to unsubscribe at the bottom of each mailer or User may contact us via our Site.

**How we protect your information?**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users' personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and Users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you are giving us your permission when you sign up or order with us.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Printfly Corporation has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site.  

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at [https://www.rushordertees.com](https://www.rushordertees.com/)

**RushOrderTees.com**  
2727 Commerce Way  
Philadelphia, PA 19154  
Tel: [800-620-1233](tel:8006201233)  
Email: [service@rushordertees.com](mailto:service@rushordertees.com)
